http://www.bestnest.com/bestnest/privacypolicy.asp

1-513-232-4225 Int'l
Call Center Hours:
Wild Birds
Gift CertificatesAccessoriesBird Feeder Trays & AccessoriesBird House ExtrasCleaning AccessoriesHummingbird Feeder AccessoriesNesting MaterialsPoles, Hooks, & HangersSquirrel BafflesWeather DomesWindow WarningsBird BathsAccessoriesFountain Bird BathsHeated Bird BathsHeaters & DeicersKits & PackagesNon-Heated Bird BathsStands & PedestalsBird FeedersBluebird FeedersCaged Bird FeedersDecorative FeedersGazebo Bird FeedersHopper FeedersHummingbird FeedersKits & PackagesOriole FeedersPlatform / Tray FeedersSpecialty Bird FeedersSquirrel Proof Bird FeedersSuet & Seed Cake FeedersTube Bird FeedersWindow Bird FeedersBird HousesBluebird HousesDecorative Bird HousesDuck HousesFinch / Swallow HousesKits & PackagesOwl & Kestrel HousesPurple Martin HousesRobin HousesWoodpecker / Flicker HousesWren / Chickadee HousesBirding ToolsDecoysSeed, Suet & FoodBird Feed Dispensers & StorageMealwormsNectar - Hummingbird, OrioleSeed Cakes, Bells & BlocksSuetWild Bird Seed
Other Wildlife
Gift CertificatesBats & Bat HousesAccessoriesBat HousesBooks & MediaKits & PackagesBee Houses & BeekeepingButterfly Houses & FeedersLadybug HousesSquirrel FeedersToad HousesWildlife Feeders
Outdoor Living
Gift CertificatesArbors, Trellises & ObelisksArbors, Arches & PergolasObelisks & PyramidsTrellisesFence, Borders, & EdgingFire & BarbecueCampfire CookingChimeneasFire PitsLog RacksMailboxes & AccessoriesMailbox PostsMailboxesOutdoor DecorChimes & BellsDoormatsFlags & BannersFountains & BubblersGarden RocksGazing Balls & StandsKites, Rockers, & SpinnersRain ChainsStatuaryStepping StonesWall Art & DecorOutdoor FurnitureBenchesChairsPicnic TablesTablesOutdoor LightingAccessoriesFirepotsLandscape LightingLanterns & TorchesSecurity LightsSolar LightingTabletop LightingPlants & Lawn CareCompostingFertilizers & Plant FoodFungicidesGarden SprayersHerbicidesInsecticidesLandscape FabricLawn & Garden ToolsPlant Caddies & TrivetsPlant Stands & HangersPlant SupportsPots & PlantersSeason Extenders & Plant AidsVasesWatering EquipmentPlaques, Signs & MarkersAddress Plaques & MarkersCommon Signs & MarkersGarden & Plant MarkersHouse NumbersMemorial Plaques & MarkersWedding PlaquesPoles, Hooks & HangersBranch, Extension & Misc HooksChain HangersDeck or Rail Mount HangersGround SocketsMetal Tubular Poles & HangersMounting Plates & AdaptersPosts, Pedestals & StandsWall or Post Mount HangersWrought Iron Shepherd HooksPools & SpasPool PumpsTie Downs
Water Gardens
Gift CertificatesAeratorsChemicals & Pond CareChlorine & Ammonia NeutralizersFish HealthMosquito ControlpH ManagementSpecialty BacteriaStartup Kits & Seasonal PrepWater ClarifiersWater Test KitsFilters, Skimmers & ClarifiersFiltersKits & PackagesSkimmers & AccessoriesUV ClarifiersFish & Fish FoodFountainsHeaters & DeicersLighting & ElectricalPond LightsPower ManagementReplacement PartsPlants & Plant CarePlumbing (Tubing & Fittings)Tubing & Fittings, 0.375"Tubing & Fittings, 0.5"Tubing & Fittings, 0.625"Tubing & Fittings, 0.75"Tubing & Fittings, 1"Tubing & Fittings, 1.25"Tubing & Fittings, 1.5"Tubing & Fittings, 2"Pond KitsPreformed PondsPond Liners & UnderlaymentPond NettingPond Pumps & PartsAccessoriesPond Pumps 0250-0899 GPH, SMPond Pumps 0900-1799 GPH, MEDPond Pumps 1800-4999 GPH, LGPond Pumps 5000+ GPH, XLPrefiltersReplacement Parts for PumpsStatuary Pumps <250 GPHStatuary & Pond DecorDecoysWaterfalls & Spillways
New Items
Hot Buys
Clearance
All Departments
Gift CertificatesBooks & MediaAudio Tapes & CDsBooksGift GuideGifts Under $25Gifts Under $50Gifts Under $100Gifts Under $250Gifts Over $250Holiday & Seasonal DecorFallWinterPatrioticOtherIn the HomeHome DecorKitchenSump, Well & Utility PumpsKids, Games & EducationalArts & CraftsGames & ToysKid's CampingKid's FurnitureKid's GardeningScience & LearningLivestock & EquineBuckets & TubsFencingPoultryStock Tank Heaters & DeicersOther WildlifeBats & Bat HousesBee Houses & BeekeepingButterfly Houses & FeedersLadybug HousesSquirrel FeedersToad HousesWildlife FeedersOutdoor LivingArbors, Trellises & ObelisksFence, Borders, & EdgingFire & BarbecueMailboxes & AccessoriesOutdoor DecorOutdoor FurnitureOutdoor LightingPlants & Lawn CarePlaques, Signs & MarkersPoles, Hooks & HangersPools & SpasTie DownsPersonalized ItemsAddress Plaques & MarkersCommon Signs & MarkersDoormatsMailboxes & AccessoriesMemorial PlaquesPlantersWedding PlaquesPest ControlBaits & LuresCats & DogsInsects & Other BugsMice & RatsSprayersWildlifePet CarePet BedsPet Bowls & WaterersPet Food StorageWater GardensAeratorsChemicals & Pond CareFilters, Skimmers & ClarifiersFountainsHeaters & DeicersLighting & ElectricalPlants & Plant CarePlumbing (Tubing & Fittings)Pond KitsPond Liners & UnderlaymentPond NettingPond Pumps & PartsStatuary & Pond DecorWaterfalls & SpillwaysWeather & TimeBarometersClocksRain GaugesSundials & Armillary SpheresThermometersUV SensorsWeather StationsWeathervanesWild BirdsAccessoriesBird BathsBird FeedersBird HousesBirding ToolsSeed, Suet & Food
Privacy Policy
Please read this policy in it's entirety.
General Online Privacy Protection
BestNest.com respects the privacy concerns of the users of its web sites.
As a general policy, no personal information is automatically collected
from users of its web sites. However, certain non-personal information is
recorded by the standard operation of the Internet servers. Information,
such as the type of browser being used, its operating system, and your
domain name is gathered in order to customize your online experience.
Other uses of this information include internal review of the number
of users to the Sites, but only in an aggregate and
non-personally-identifiable form.
Personally identifiable information that may be collected in connection
with your voluntarily filling out forms in the checkout process or other
areas of the site is retained by BestNest.com. This information may be used to better
understand your use of the site and may be sold or otherwise
transferred outside the company.
Children's Online Privacy Protection
BestNest.com does not collect information specially related to children, age or
gender. Just as with adults, personal information about or obtained from a
child will not be used for commercial or trade purposes.
Only legal adults
may make a credit card purchase on the BestNest.com web site. Children age 13 or
under may not make any purchase but their parents or legal guardians may make the
purchase for them.
Illegal Activity, Fraud or Non-Payment for Merchandise
In the event of any illegal activity on the BestNest.com web sites, we reserve
the right to turn over the information collected to the appropriate authorities,
lawyers and credit collection personnel. This includes attempts to hack into or
otherwise compromise the BestNest.com web sites.
Also included is any fraudulent use
of credit cards, checks, money orders or wire transfers.
BestNest.com reserves the right to use all legal means to recover payment for any
orders shipped.
This includes non-payment as a result of credit card chargebacks
or disputes, and checks with insufficient funds or stop payment.
If you have any specific questions related to any of the information contained on
this page please contact BestNest.com Customer Service at
customerservice@bestnest.com.
Phone: 513-232-4225   Fax: 513-232-4118   Email: customerservice@bestnest.com
TOLL FREE 1-877-562-1818
Friday, December 11, 2020
